http://www.pbbanking.com/terms-of-use

Terms of Use
PLEASE REVIEW THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE (“SITE”). PEOPLES BANK (“THE “BANK”), PROVIDES ACCESS TO THIS WEBSITE AND ITS PRODUCTS AND SERVICES SUBJECT TO THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE (“TERMS”).General LimitationsThis Site has been established by the Bank for the sole purpose of conveying information about the Bank’s products and services and to allow communication between the Bank and its customers. Nothing contained in any page on this Site takes the place of the Bank’s agreements and disclosures that govern its products and services. If any information on the Site conflicts with that in the Bank’s agreements and disclosures, the agreements and disclosures will control.The information and materials contained in this Site are owned by the Bank or by others, as applicable. No material may be copied,displayed, transmitted, distributed, framed, sold, stored for use, downloaded,or otherwise reproduced except as permitted by law.By accessing this Site, you are agreeing to be bound by these Site Terms, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this Site. The materials contained in this Site are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.Peoples Bank reserves the right to revise the Terms at any time, without notice. You can review the most recent Terms at www.pbbanking.com.Use of the SiteIn order to use the Site, you must obtain access to the Internet via an Internet Service Provider and you must use appropriate and compatible hardware and software. You are solely responsible for any fees incurred to access the Internet and our Site. Peoples Bank operates a secure Site, using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption and requires that you use a web browser that supports SSL. Peoples Bank is not responsible for any computer virus or other errors that may be associated with the use of our Site.All products and services provided by Peoples Bank are subject to the terms and conditions of each service. Product offers, terms,rates and product information are subject to change without notice.Privacy PolicyYour privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use,communicate and disclose and make use of personal information gathered through your use of our Site. For additional information on how we share information,please review our Privacy Notice.· Peoples Bank reserves the right to place “cookies” on your computer to manage preferences you have entered and for user authentication purposes.· Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.· We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes,unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.· We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.· We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.· We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.· We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.Protectionof Children Using Our SiteThe safety and security of children is very important to Peoples Bank. The online financial services offered through Peoples Bank’s Site are not designed for or directed towards children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly solicit or collect personal identifiable information from children without parental or guardian consent. Should we receive online information from any child, we will only use this information to respond directly to the child’s request, notify parents, or seek parental or guardian consent.If you believe your child has provided personally identifiable information to us, please contact Customer Care at 866.378.9500.For more information about the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act(COPPA), please visit the Federal Trade Commission website at www.ftc.gov.Copyright and TrademarksThe trademarks, trade names, and service marks used on the Peoples Bank Site are the property of Peoples Bank. No one is authorized to use any trademarks, trade names or service marks in any manner without the prior express written permission of Peoples Bank. All materials provided on the Peoples Bank Site are protected by U.S. and international copyright law, and shall not be transmitted, broadcast, copied, adapted, displayed, reproduced,republished, uploaded, downloaded, posted, distributed, performed or other wise used without the prior express written permission of Peoples Bank.Third Party ContentFrom time to time the Bank may place links to other websites on this Site. Peoples Bank has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Peoples Bank of the site.Use of any such linked web site is at your own risk. The Bank has no control over any other website and is not responsible for the content on any website other than this one. Users assume all responsibility when they go to other sites via the links on this Site.No WarrantiesThe materials on Peoples Bank’s Site are provided “as is”. Peoples Bank makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and here by disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation,implied warranties or conditions of merchant ability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, Peoples Bank does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this Site.LimitationsIn no event shall Peoples Bank or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or lost profits, or due to business interruption) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Peoples Bank’s Site, even if Peoples Bank or a Peoples Bank authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. This limitation includes, but is not limited to the omission of information, the failure of equipment, the delay or inability to receive or transmit information, the delay or inability to print information, the transmission of any computer virus, or the transmission of any other malicious or disabling code or procedure. This limitation applies even if the Bank has been informed of the possibility of such loss or damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.IndemnificationTo the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, you agree to release, Indemnify, defend and hold harmless Peoples Bank from and against all damages, claims, liabilities and expenses (including attorneys’fees) brought by any person arising from or relating to your access and use of the Site, including, without limitation, any claims alleging facts that if true would constitute a breach by user of these terms and conditions.
